[{"answer": ".", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "What -- what's been going on there?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, charity should begin at home and there's a tremendous amount of work being done and certainly we have to pay attention to -- you know, we haven't really dealt with Katrina.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What do you say to the skeptics?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "I spend, you know, hours a day on it.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "How much emotional energy are you expending on this?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "I have to say, you have a very nice tie and I know you -- you could be George.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Why does this cause mean so much to you?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "You know, not really.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "How -- how close have you come to getting hurt?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Have you discovered that you're braver than you may have thought you were?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "The answer to that question is yes.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "As a father, do you worry about George when he goes off on these crusades there?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "I think -- I think a lot of times and I think most newsmen would agree, my father being one of them, that it's not just necessarily hard news sell the Sudan, it's a hard news sell virtual -- many, many of the hot spots around the world that it's, you know, it's hard to get Burma on the news.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Why -- why are you constantly fighting this kind of uphill struggle?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "You bet.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Nick, as George's father again, do you get incensed on his behalf?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Almost never.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "And do you -- do you use maybe juicier language than that?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "George, do you -- do you believe there's going to be peace in Sudan in the next few years or are you quite pessimistic about that?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Are you worried for your own personal safety that the more high-profile you get?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Well, I love the fact that -- that they covered themselves not taking pictures.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "First of all, what was your feeling when those photographers decided to exact their horrific revenge and lay down their cameras?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "It's not just the Sudan.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "You know, I have no -- I couldn't really argue for or against that issue.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Do they have any rights to privacy when they do that?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Having whacked the media, I guess, for that part of it, obviously -- maybe come back to you, George, here.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Is there some way that a person may be allowed to go out and have dinner with his family or her family without having a camera in the nose of the three year old?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Well, the -- the -- but the deal is struck long before, you know, I got involved.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "So there is the -- I mean, there is a deal with the devil to be struck, isn't there, when it's important?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "You know, look, I thought that President Obama gave, as he does when -- when he needs to -- he gave one of the greatest speeches I've heard in a long, long time.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "What -- where do you think the line should be drawn here?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Really, I mean, honestly, my job is as good as they get.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "It can't be any worse than being a movie star, can it?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "I -- do you think he's better looking than I am?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "You've got to hope, George.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Because we see that working so well right now?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "We're making it a three-parter, now.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Is this a half-an-hour show?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "My father taught me never to mix grain and grape at a very young age.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "What values do you think they instilled in you as a young -- a young George?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Now, listen, you know, I'm very lucky.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "But to be serious -- to be serious, what -- what did they teach you?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Well let's see, the proudest I have been of George is -- you know, there's something about -- let me put it this way.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "What -- what's been the proudest you've ever been of George and also the least proud?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "You know, naughty, yes.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "ORGAN: What's the naughtiest he's ever been would you say?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I know what -- I know what you mean here and I'd like to think that I had something to do with both of the kids and how they turned out.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "What was -- what was important to you that when he grew up, he -- he'd adhere to a certain code of behavior as far as you're concerned?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I was thinking about that when you asked the question.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "But if you were to actually take your life to date, if you could replay one moment in your life before you die, what would it be?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "But it turns out it's actually this -- I mean you -- you do get malaria flare ups quite regularly, do you?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Oh, you wouldn't swap his life for yours?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "It's perfect one.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "That's a great title, is it?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "George, is he right?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Here we go.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Do you think you'll ever -- will you ever re-marry, George?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "-- for the last segment to pull it out.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "I'm allowed one, am I?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "I just got re-married.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Piers, are you married?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yeah.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Oh, you did?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think -- I don't ever wish I wasn't super rich.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "You could give it all to these people?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "I will.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Would you tell them that?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "I think he might.", "docId": "110121pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Do you think he's going to run?", "qSentId": 671}]